下一首歌 我觉得 是一首反映离家之苦的歌
再来一次
我的失误，唱低了，我错了
我们再试一次  试试这个调
谢谢 唱得太棒了 非常感谢！
I asked her to stay
我请她留下
But she wouldn't listen
但她不会听的
She left before I had the chance to say
在我有机会表达之前她已离开了
The words that were mend
弥补的言辞
the things that were broken
破碎的一切
But now its far too late she's gone away
但现在一切都太晚了，她早已离开
Every night you cry yourself to sleep
每天泪水伴你入睡
Thinking why does this happen to me
思量着为什么自己这么倒霉
Why does every moment have to be so hard
为什么美时每刻都是这么痛苦
Hard to believe that
难以相信这些
It's not over tonight
今晚仍然不会平静
Just give me one more chance to make it right
请给我一次机会去弥补
I may not make it through the night
每晚都难以入睡
I won't go home without you
没有你我不愿回家
The taste of her breath, I'll never get over
永远也忘不了曾经感受到她呼吸的那一刻
And the noises that she make keep me awake
她的吵闹声此刻令我清醒
The weight of things that remain unspoken
事情的重要性仍然未知
Built up so much it crushed us everyday
用心的构建却让我们每一天都觉得身心疲惫
Every night you cry yourself to sleep
每晚泪水伴你入睡
Thinking why does this happen to me
思量着为什么自己这么倒霉
Why does every moment have to be so hard
为什么每时每刻都是这么痛苦
Hard to believe that
难以相信这些
It's not over tonight
今晚仍然不会平静
Just give me one more chance to make it right
请给我一次机会去弥补
I may not make it through the night
每晚都难以入睡
I won't go home without you
没有你我不愿回家
Of all the things I felt I've never really showed
我没能将所有的一切都告诉你
perhaps the worst is that I ever let you go
但是最糟糕的是我居然曾经让你离开
should not ever let you go oh oh oh
我本不该让你走的，噢
It's not over tonight
今晚仍然不会平静
Just give me one more chance to make it right
请给我一次机会去弥补
I may not make it through the night
每晚都难以入睡
I won't go home without you
没有你我不愿回家
It's not over tonight
今晚仍然不会平静
Just give me one more chance to make it right
请给我一次机会去弥补
I may not make it through the night
每晚都难以入睡
I won't go home without you
没有你我不愿回家
谢谢大家